sony.ca 2015-06-13

# Sony CA

Sony of Canada Ltd. ("Sony") respects your right to personal privacy. When we collect your personal information ("Personal Information"), you can be confident that we'll handle and store it in a secure manner to protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

This code describes our privacy practices. By purchasing a product or service, submitting a warranty card, participating in our web sites, or otherwise providing us with your Personal Information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Code. These terms and conditions are subject to change from time to time, so you should review them for changes periodically. Please note that anonymous data from which you cannot be identified is excluded from the restrictions described in this Privacy Code. 

### Why do we collect your personal information?

Our goal at Sony is to provide our customers with the highest quality products and services. In order to process and record your purchases, and to ensure that you receive quality products and customer services, we collect certain Personal Information directly from our customers.

You can visit Sony's retail stores or our web sites without identifying yourself or providing any Personal Information. At certain times, however, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to complete a transaction, provide you with important product information, enhance your visit or follow up later. Your participation is completely optional.

For example, we request information when you:

  * • purchase a product or service;
  * • register as a member of one of our programs;
  * • register a product warranty;
  * • purchase a Sony Care extended warranty;
  * • complete a survey;
  * • participate in a contest or other promotional offer;
  * • subscribe to a newsletter or mailing list;
  * • apply for employment

In these instances, we may ask for your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, information about a product you have purchased, billing or credit card information, or other information. We may also keep records of previous purchases made by you, information we have provided to you, and details of any enquires, complaints or compliments made by you and our response, if any (referred to as your "Personal History"). Your Personal Information and Personal History will be added to our customer database.

### Automatic Information Collection and Monitoring on our Websites.

For each visitor to a Sony website, Sony's web server automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor's IP address/domain name combination and any referring websites. We use this information to understand visitor traffic patterns through our websites for purposes of enhancing their usability. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you have activated blocking technology available in some browsers.

When you visit Sony websites or advertisements appearing thereon, or use one or more of Sony's website services, we may use an industry-wide technology called "cookies' that store certain information on your computer and that allow us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences, or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies, we may not be able to restore any preferences or customize settings you previously specified, and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

Sony may but is not obligated to monitor communications such as messages to, from, within or directly related to our services and websites to ensure that our policies regarding use and our terms and conditions are being complied with and are not being violated (e.g. no obscenity, defamation or abusive language, no content that may infringe legal rights), and Sony has the right to block, remove and/or report any such communications and activities as appropriate. We may keep records of user's messages and, among other things, the email addresses involved. By accessing a Sony website or application, you acknowledge and consent to such monitoring.

### What do we do with your personal information?

The primary purpose of our collection of this information is to be able to provide products and services to you, to provide you with customer support services, to seek your opinion from time to time, and to compile marketing and other statistics for use by Sony. Sony may also use this information with data from third parties to provide information to you on Sony products, services and promotions, and on complementary products and services offered by our affiliated companies and other companies. At times we collect Personal Information with third parties, who may also keep your Personal Information.

When we do so, the identity of the third party will be made known to you. Personal History information is primarily used for customer support, statistical and customer services purposes.

Your Personal Information and Personal History will be kept confidential and used to enrich your customer relationship with Sony. For instance, we may inform you of product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new Sony products and services we feel may be of interest to you. When you visit our company web sites, we want to help you find information quickly and to personalize your visits.

### We protect your personal information

We will not share your Personal Information with anyone outside Sony and its affiliated companies, except to the extent necessary to fulfill the purposes described or where we have collected Personal Information with a third party as noted above. When we employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf – such as delivering products, sending postal or electronic mail, analyzing data, taking product orders, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing other forms of service – and where we collect Personal Information with third parties, we ensure by contractual means that these third parties may not use your Personal Information for any other purpose without your knowledge and consent. 

Your personal information may be maintained and processed by our affiliates and other third party service providers in the US or other jurisdictions. Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes.

### Our Information Policy Re: Children

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information to Sony without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If we learn that you are under 13 years of age, we will not use any personally identifiable information about you without the consent of your parents or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities offered by Sony without that consent.

In some circumstances, we may ask our customers and web site visitors to provide us with contact information of their parent or guardian. We will use this information only for the purpose of contacting the parent or guardian to notify them of our information practices with respect to children, to notify that person of a child's participation in one of our promotional activities or on one of our web sites, and/or to seek the consent of the parent or guardian to such participation.

The parent or guardian of any person under the age of 13 whose Personal Information we have collected may ask to review that Personal Information and to have it deleted (subject to certain restrictions). For more information on how to do this, please contact Sony as indicated below.

### Legal, Government & Other Disclosures

Sony, our affiliates and our Canadian, US and other service providers may provide your Personal Information and Personal History Information to appropriate third parties including law enforcement or other government agencies in connection with a criminal investigation, fraud prevention or other legal action, or if Sony reasonably believes it is necessary to protect Sony including its systems and operations, its customers or the public, or as otherwise required by applicable Canadian, US or other law.

Sony web sites may contain links to other sites. Sony and its affiliates are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites and expressly disclaim all liability associated with your use of and the content on such other sites. 

### We encourage communication

Customers who want more information about our privacy policy, wish access to their Personal Information, or wish to raise a concern about the use of their Personal Information, can contact Sony at 1-888-494-7669 or by writing to the Privacy Office, Sony of Canada Ltd., 115 Gordon Baker Road, Toronto, Ontario M2H 3R6, Attention: Chief Privacy Officer. Subject to certain limitations, you may review, correct or update your Personal Information, limit or revoke consent for disclosure or use or, in certain circumstances, have your Personal Information deleted. We will keep your Personal Information for a reasonable period or time in order to fulfill your primary business purpose, or as required or permitted by law or business custom, whichever is longer.

If you no longer wish to receive communications from Sony of Canada Ltd. you can click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of a commercial electronic message from Sony of Canada Ltd. or you can contact us:

**By Phone:** Toll-free (within Canada) 1-888-494-7669

**By Mail:** Sony of Canada Ltd.,  
115 Gordon Baker Road,  
Toronto, Ontario, M2H 3R6  
Attn: Privacy Officer, Law Department

Personal Information submitted to us in any application for employment is not used for marketing purposes.
